login

register

email

password

submit

Animal Lovers
-------------

Register on Cuddly to view your past donations.

Shelter/Rescues
---------------

Start a Fundraiser, Add Wishlists, and Share Adoptable Pets.

Cart

Privacy Policy
==============

**PRIVACY POLICY**

LAST UPDATED -  August, 2021 

CUDDLY, Inc. respects your privacy concerns. This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") describes the types of personal information we collect, how we use the information and with whom we share it. Based on the services we offer, CUDDLY, Inc. is a data processor of information you provide and only act on this information on your behalf (see our Terms of Use at https://cuddly.com/terms-conditions) and the data controller for the data you provide to access our services and make purchases. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you contact CUDDLY, Inc. by emailing support@CUDDLY.com. You may also write to us at the address below. The phrase 'personal information' refers to information by which you or the device you are using to connect to the Internet is identified.

CUDDLY Inc. is registered in the United States with an office at -

909 Electric Ave. #208,

Seal Beach, CA 90740.

**TYPES OF INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT**

You may visit our Cuddly.com without providing any personal information, although we will collect certain statistical information discussed below. If you contact us to obtain information about our products or services, we may collect your name, phone number, email or street address along with other information you may choose to submit. If you create a CUDDLY, Inc. account, we may collect your name and email address and ask you to choose a username and password. By providing information to us, you agree to our collection and use as described in this Privacy Policy.

Also, the other modes of data collection may include:

· Offline Collection. We also receive your name and contact information from you when you provide it to us in-person, through the mail or on a telephone call, at an event, or when you surrender or adopt an animal. Some of the information you provide to us offline may be used to automatically create an online account for you, which you can access via our Services.

· Communications. We receive information from you when you contact us or we communicate with you, including via email, phone, or social media.

· Cookies and Other Similar Technologies. We, and our service providers, use various technologies to collect and store information when you use our Services, and this may include sending 'cookies' to your device. For more information on our use of cookies, please see the "Cookies" section below.

· Analytics software. When you use our Services, we and our service providers, such as website analytics, social media widgets, and online ad networks, may receive certain information from your use of our Services, including, but not limited to the actions you take on our Services, the web pages or sites that you visit just before or just after you use our Services, the dates and times that you use our Services, and device information such as your IP address, locale, operating system, and web browser. Service providers such as analytics providers may collect information about your online activities over time and across different online services when you use our Services.

· Information from Third Parties. We like to know about the individuals who make donations to us, so we can communicate with them more effectively and adjust our outreach efforts. For this reason, we may collect information from third parties about our donors, including demographic and contact information, and combine it with information we collect from donors.

**USING THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

We will only use the personal information we collect from and about you for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy and when the law allows us to do so. We will generally use your personal information on the following lawful grounds:

\- Where the use of your personal information is necessary for the performance of a contract we are about to enter into or have entered into with you;

\- Where the use is necessary for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party);

\- Where we need to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation; or

\- Where you have provided your consent to opt-in to marketing from the Non-Profit you have donated to.

We may use the information that you provide us or that we obtain about you for a variety of business purposes in our legitimate interests, including the following: (i) to manage and maintain your account; (ii) process and track your payments; including confirmations and invoices (iii) contact you about your donations and your account, and contact individuals (i.e. guests) at your request and on your behalf; (iv) maintain a record of the payments you make on our Website; (v) communicate with you about our Website, products, services, offers, and events, donation opportunities, administrative messages, or other news or information about us, send you marketing communications jointly with our partners, provide you with personalized online advertising, mail, email, and telephone marketing messages provided you have given your consent if required under local law; (vi) have our customer support team respond to your questions, requests, and comments; (vii) Monitor and analyze trends, usage, and activities in connection with our Services to operate, evaluate and improve our Website; (viii) send marketing communications, including email, to identify when emails sent to you have been received and track industry standard performance metrics, such as email opens and clicks; (ix) investigate and prevent fraud and unauthorized transactions and identify potential hackers and other unauthorized access to our Services, and other illegal activities; (x) enforce our Terms of Use; and (xi) comply with legal requirements, industry standards and our policies; (xii) Provide, improve, personalize, and promote our Services; (xiii) Develop new services, features, and functionality; (xiv) Comply with your requests and permitted uses.

**HOW WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION**

We do not sell or otherwise disclose personal information that you provide us or that we obtain to companies, organizations, or individuals outside of our organization unless you request, consent or authorize us to do so, except as described in this Privacy Policy.

We may share the personal information that you provide to us, and the information that we collect about you to support our business interests as described above, to others, such as to

1\. We will not sell, share, or trade our donor lists containing personal information, including names, email addresses, mailing addresses, and phone numbers, with any other non-affiliated organization, and non-participating non-profits for their purposes, unless donors have given us specific permission to do so. This limitation includes personal information received online or offline by us from or about our donors in connection with requesting and/or processing donations. We will share information with service providers that will use the donors' information only as necessary to provide their services to us. For example, we may use an email service provider to send newsletters and other communications to our donors. We may also share it with merchant partners so that they might provide fulfillment and payment processing services and customer support services to fulfill your purchase(s) and handle any issues with our services. We may share your information with our service providers and vendors, such as technology, direct mailing, online advertising, telephone calling, and analytics services. We also provide your payment information to our service provider for payment processing and verification. We do not send mailings to our donors on behalf of other organizations, unless they have given us specific permission to do so.

2\. Analytics service providers to ensure site functionality and enable data-driven business decisions; to provide, improve, personalize, and promote our Services; develop new services, features, and functionality.

3\. Comply with the law, applicable regulations, governmental and quasi-governmental requests, court orders or subpoenas, to enforce our agreements or to protect our rights, property or safety or the rights, property or safety of our users or others.

4\. Marketing or advertising service providers and networks to send marketing communications as well as serve you ads tailored to your interests or to tailor ads that may be served to you on our Website, as well as other websites and social media networks. You may see certain ads on other websites because we participate in advertising networks. Ad networks allow us to target our advertising to users through demographic, behavioral and contextual means. These networks track your online activities over time by collecting information through automated means, including the use of cookies, web beacons and other methods. The networks use this information to show you advertisements that are tailored to your interests. The information our ad network vendors collect includes information about your visit to the Website as well as pages you have viewed, and the actions you have taken on the Website.

5\. When you make a donation using our Services, we may disclose your email, name, donation amount, and your comments to the person who requested a donation from you. With your consent, we may post your name and donation amount publicly on our Services, where the information is viewable by other users and the public. We are not responsible for the actions of users who view and use the posted information.

6\. Our Services may allow you to share information with social networking websites, such as Facebook. We do not share your information with them unless you direct us to share it. Their use of the information will be governed by their privacy policies, and you may be able to modify your privacy settings on their websites.

7\. We may disclose your information to a third party if (a) we believe that disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, (b) to enforce our agreements, policies and terms of service, (c) to protect the security or integrity of our Services, (d) to protect the property, rights, and safety of us, our animals, our users, donors, or the public from harm or illegal activities, (e) to respond to an emergency which we believe in the good faith requires us to disclose information to assist in preventing the death or serious bodily injury of any person, or (f) to investigate and defend ourselves or others against any third-party claims or allegations.

If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, sale of assets, or other business transaction, your information may be sold or transferred as part of such a transaction as permitted by law and/or contract. We cannot control how such entities may use or disclose such information

We also use non-personally identifiable information in the aggregate so that we can improve our Services and for business and administrative purposes. We may also use or share with third parties as listed above for any purpose aggregated data that contains no personally identifiable information.

**INFORMATION SHARING OPTIONS**

We offer you certain choices about the collection, use, and sharing of your information. Withdrawing your consent to use your personal information may mean that you cannot take advantage of certain offerings or Website features.

Marketing Communications - You may choose not to receive marketing email communications from us by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the marketing emails.

Even after you opt out from receiving promotional messages from us, you will continue to receive administrative messages from us regarding our Services.

Targeted Advertising - If you do not wish to have us collect, use and share information about you to deliver targeted online advertising in this manner, please click here (http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) and follow the instructions of how to opt-out. Please also note that most opt-out mechanisms are cookie-based and will only affect the specific computer and browser that is used to submit an opt-out request. If you have multiple computers or change computers, or use multiple browsers, you will need to submit opt-out requests for each such computer or browser. Besides, if you delete, block or otherwise restrict cookies, you will need to renew the opt-out choices to ensure that any opt-out cookies remain effective.

Cookies - Most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable existing cookies.

We may use cookies and other technologies to collect and store information such as the dates and times you visit our Services and the pages or content that you visit, and to provide and improve our Services, and better understand how you interact with our Services. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information. If you have set your browser to reject cookies, you can still use our Services, although you may need to re-enter information we would normally obtain from the cookie and some functions of our Services may not work. Third party websites linked to our Services may also use cookies and may track your activities across websites and over time. We are not responsible for cookies placed by third parties.

We may show you personalized advertising on our Services and other websites. We currently use personalized advertising with Google AdWords to display content-specific advertisements to visitors that have previously visited our Services when those visitors go to other websites that have the Google Display Network implemented.

We and other third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party and third-party cookies together to inform and serve ads based on a visitor's past visits to our websites.

You may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting Google's Ads Settings at any time. You can also install the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on available here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout and employ it at the start of each session on our Website. A cookie will be set on your browser that instructs this technology not to start for that session. Please note that the next time you access the Website the analytics will be reactivated, so you will have to disable the technology each time. If you reject the cookies and web-beacons we use, you may still use certain aspects of the Website, but you will not be maximizing the value of the Website.

We also use Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting and Google collects and processes certain Services-usage data. Google provides additional privacy options regarding cookie-use for analytics described at

 Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of all of our Websites' features. Disabling cookies may cancel opt-outs that rely on cookies, such as web analytics or targeted advertising opt-outs.

Third Party Data Collection - We permit limited third parties to place cookies through our Website to provide us with better insights into the use of our Website or user demographics or to provide relevant advertising to you. These third parties may collect information about a consumer's online activities over time and across different websites when he or she uses our Website.

**YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To submit your request, please email support@CUDDLY.com with the subject line "California Privacy" and your request in the body of your email.

**INTERNATIONAL USERS AND WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Our Services are hosted in the United States.The personal information that you provide to us is generally stored on servers located in the United States through third party cloud services. If you choose to use our Services from other regions of the world, including the EU with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law (less or more stringent), then please note that we will transfer your information outside of those regions to the United States for storage and processing. By using our website, or providing your information, , including without limitation users in the European Union, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to such storage and processing in the United States and the collection, transfer, processing, use, storage, and disclosure of your information per this privacy policy in the United States.

**HOW LONG WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We retain your data while your account is in existence or as needed to provide you our services and for legitimate and essential business purposes, such as maintaining the performance of CUDDLY, making data-driven business decisions, complying with our legal obligations, and resolving disputes. If you request, we will delete or anonymize your data so that it no longer identifies you, unless, we are legally allowed or required to maintain certain personal data, including (without limitation) situations such as the following:

\- If there is an unresolved issue relating to your accounts, such as an outstanding credit on your account or an unresolved claim or dispute we will retain the necessary personal data until the issue is resolved;

\- Where we are required to retain the personal data for our legal, tax, audit, and accounting obligations, we will retain the necessary personal data for the period required by applicable law; and/or,

\- Where necessary for our legitimate business interests such as fraud prevention or to maintain the security of our users.

**ACCESSING AND UPDATING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

You may access and update your registration information by reaching out to us at support@CUDDLY.com. You can update preferences to receive email or other communications by clicking unsubscribe on emails you receive from Cuddly or the Non-profit you opted-in to receiving marketing from. These parties will take commercially reasonable steps to implement your opt-out requests promptly, but you may still receive communications from us for up to ten business days as we process your request. If you believe other personal information we maintain about you is inaccurate, you may request that we correct or amend the information by contacting us at support@CUDDLY.com with the subject line "Update Account Information" and your request in the body of your email. While we make efforts to accommodate requests to restrict our use of your information, we reserve the right to delete all or any portion of customer information if we are not able to reasonably accommodate a requested restriction.

**LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES**

Our Website may contain links to websites operated and maintained by third parties, over which we have no control. Privacy policies on such linked websites may be different from our Privacy Policy. You access such linked websites at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a linked website before disclosing any of your information on such website. We are not responsible for the actions of those other sites, the content of their sites, or any products or services they may offer.

**SECURITY**

We maintain reasonable physical, electronic, administrative, and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of information transmitted to us. To guard your information delivered to us electronically, our Website uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) to protect credit card processing information and access controls to protect against unauthorized access to your personal information. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Despite our efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable and no method of data transmission can be guaranteed against any interception or other type of misuse. As a result, while we strive to protect your contact information, to the extent permitted by law, we do not guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from our Website, and you do so at your own risk.

We urge you to keep any password that you establish with us in a safe place and not to divulge it to anyone. Also, remember to log off your account and close your browser window when you have finished your visit. This is to ensure that others cannot access your account, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place.

By using our Services or providing information to us, you agree that we may communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of our Services. If we learn of a security system's breach, we may attempt to notify you electronically by posting a notice on our Services or sending an email to you.

**CHILDREN'S PRIVACY AND PARENTAL CONTROLS**

We do not solicit any personal information from children. If you are not 18 or older, you are not authorized to use the Website. Parents should be aware that there are parental control tools available online that you can use to prevent your children from submitting information online without parental permission or from accessing material that is harmful to minors. If we become aware that a child under 18 has provided us with personal information, we will promptly take steps to delete such information. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us at support@cuddly.com.

**PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES**

We may change this privacy policy from time to time. If we make any changes, we will notify you by revising the "LAST UPDATED" date at the bottom of this privacy policy. If the changes materially alter your rights or obligations hereunder, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you of the change. For example, we may send a message to your email address, if we have one on file, or generate a pop-up or similar notification when you access our Services for the first time after such material changes are made. Your continued use of our Services after the revised policy has become effective indicates that you have read, understood, and agreed to the current version of this policy.

**Mobile Message Service Terms and Conditions**

Last updated: 10/14/2021

The Cuddly mobile message service (the "Service") is operated by Cuddly, Inc. ("Cuddly, Inc." , "we", or "us"). Your use of the Service constitutes your agreement to these terms and conditions ("Mobile Terms"). We may modify or cancel the Service or any of its features without notice. To the extent permitted by applicable law, we may also modify these Mobile Terms at any time and your continued use of the Service following the effective date of any such changes shall constitute your acceptance of such changes.

By consenting to Cuddly's SMS/text messaging service, you agree to receive recurring SMS/text messages with service-related and promotional messages, including updates, alerts, and information (e.g., order updates, account alerts, etc.) and promotions, specials, and other marketing offers (e.g., cart reminders)\] from and on behalf of Cuddly via text messages through your wireless provider to the mobile number you provided, even if your mobile number is registered on any state or federal Do Not Call list. Text messages may be sent using an automatic telephone dialing system or other technology.

You understand that you do not have to sign up for this program in order to make any purchases, and your consent is not a condition of any purchase with Cuddly . Your participation in this program is completely voluntary.

We do not charge for the Service, but you are responsible for all charges and fees associated with text messaging imposed by your wireless provider. Message frequency varies. Standard message and data rates may apply from your wireless provider. Check your mobile plan and contact your wireless provider for details. You are solely responsible for all charges related to SMS/text messages, including charges from your wireless provider.

You may opt-out of the Service at any time. Text the single keyword command STOP to \[insert your sending number\] . Click the unsubscribe link in any text message to cancel. You'll receive a one-time opt-out confirmation text message. No further messages will be sent to your mobile device, unless initiated by you. If you have subscribed to other Cuddly mobile message programs and wish to cancel, except where applicable law requires otherwise, you will need to opt out separately from those programs by following the instructions provided in their respective mobile terms. For Service support or assistance, text HELP to (833)735-1867 or email support@cuddly.com .

We may change any short code or telephone number we use to operate the Service at any time and will notify you of these changes. You acknowledge that any messages, including any STOP or HELP requests, you send to a short code or telephone number we have changed may not be received and we will not be responsible for honoring requests made in such messages.

The wireless carriers supported by the Service are not liable for delayed or undelivered messages. You agree to provide us with a valid mobile number. If you get a new mobile number, you will need to sign up for the program with your new number.

To the extent permitted by applicable law, you agree that we will not be liable for failed, delayed, or misdirected delivery of any information sent through the Service, any errors in such information, and/or any action you may or may not take in reliance on the information or Service.

We respect your right to privacy. To see how we collect and use your personal information, please see our Privacy Notice.

**CONTACT US**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at support@CUDDLY.com.

You may also write to us at:

CUDDLY, Inc.

c/o Privacy Policy

909 Electric Ave. #208

Seal Beach, CA 90740

about

give

help

legal

[

BBB Rating: A-](https://www.bbb.org/us/ca/seal-beach/profile/animal-shelter/cuddly-1126-1000062093)

© The CUDDLY Group, Inc. All Rights Reserved.

Register with CUDDLY today!
---------------------------

CHOOSE ONE TO PROCEED

Animal Lovers
-------------

Register on Cuddly to view your past donations.

[CONTINUE](https://register.cuddly.com/user) Already registered? [Log In](https://cuddly.com/login) here!

Shelter/Rescues
---------------

Start a Fundraiser, Add Wishlists, and Share Adoptable Pets.

[CONTINUE](https://cuddly.com/register) Already registered? [Log In](https://cuddly.com/login) here!
